CAREER PROFILE

I am a qualified Diagnostic Radiographer with an ambition to aid in improving health care, patient care and making the patients' health care experience a positive one. I am an honest, reliable, responsible and hardworking individual and I hope to make a difference in the healthcare field. References available upon request

EXPERIENCE

Community Service Diagnostic Radiographer

Manguzi Hospital

- I learnt how to operate dark room equipment.
- I learnt a sufficient amount of isiZulu to be able to communicate effectively with my patients.

Jan. 2019 - Dec. 2019

Jan. 2015 - Dec. 2018

Jan. 2015 - Dec. 2018

• I learnt how to work independently due to 'on-call' and after-hour shifts being worked alone.

Student Diagnostic Radiographer CPUT

• Thesis (2018): CT vs MRI in diagnosing glioblastomas of the brain

Student Diagnostic Radiographer

Various Hospitals

- Hospitals include: Groote Schuur Hospital, Victoria Hospital, Red-cross Children's Hospital, Somerset Hospital, Retreat Day Hospital, Bishop Lavis Day Hospital
- Interacted with patients, developing patient care and inter-personal skills as well as an empathetic outlook towards health care
- Computer and technology literacy, while working with the medical machinery and computers
- I successfully completed a course in information literacy and was awarded distinction. (Apr. 2015)
- Worked in a team environment, learning the value of teamwork and also working independently
- While at university I learnt various skills including:
 - time management through completion of assignments
 - o leadership qualities through being appointed leader in multiple group projects
 - o organizational qualities through planning and delegating tasks

EXTRAMURAL

Au Pair

I have been babysitting for 10 years. From this I have learnt how to handle responsibilities and expectations placed upon me.

Soccer and netball

I have been playing team sports for a number of years and it has taught me social skills and how to be a team player, attributes I hope to utilise in my work environment.



chardeqriffiths@gmail.cor

(+27) 71 869 8618

EDUCATION

BSc (Hons) Diagnostic Radiography - Cum Laude Cape Peninsula University of Technology Jan. 2015 - Dec. 2018

LANGUAGES

English (native)

INTERESTS

Hiking / Trail-running

Soccer and netball

Animals

Travelling